<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-29T18:04:05+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ADEM</title><subtitle>Personal website of Marcus Ng.</subtitle><author><name>Marcus Ng</name><email>marcus.ng@chem.gla.ac.uk</email></author><entry><title type="html">First website</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First website" /><published>2020-05-13T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/first-post/">&lt;p&gt;Creating a website seemed like a daunting tasks especially for a person like myself without any background or any 
“computer wizards” in my extended family. &lt;br /&gt;
I am certain that the idea of having a personal website has came across into most people’s mind but “where do I start?”,
“don’t I need a professional website designer and/or programmer to do such a difficult tasks?” are the questions that
I’ve always asked myself. &lt;br /&gt;
I was fortunate enough to have a &lt;em&gt;post-doc&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.juanma.io/&quot;&gt;Juanma&lt;/a&gt; who have suggested “Why don’t you try 
Jekyll? You can write the posts and most of the things in markdown format”. I had a look and started/attempted to make 
it with Jekyll, but it was still a bit challenging for me with all the layouts and I just wanted a nice simple layout
that I can just plug and go. &lt;br /&gt;
So I did what most people who started out programming do, I looked into github and just try to clone and edit what’s 
available out there, and in this case it’s Juanma’s website. He had adopted his layout from minimal-mistakes and I have 
adopted my layout from his layout. #thecircleoflife &lt;br /&gt;
In any case, I hope he doesn’t mind me doing it and perhaps he’ll never find out about my personal website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Marcus Ng</name><email>marcus.ng@chem.gla.ac.uk</email></author><summary type="html">I have finally gathered my courage to make a personal website</summary></entry></feed>